Jhalda Pimple
religious big crop is taking 530 10 top
and yesterday's high school is the top topic, one
friend has seen positive proportion
and if we look at the technical also, then here
in the very short term we see the MB target and the
target of 80 and Tukda ji, when
I saw the chart for the first time, I thought it was a
printout of triple bottom but after
looking carefully it seems that the effect of love triangle pattern is seen
coming here, so it is
very beneficial, buy and go,
keep a small stop loss 469, hardly four to five
rupees below the stop loss,
buy at 469, the first target in BPCL will be
₹400, keep an eye on the channel, it is
coming in the moment, the theft has started from four hundred and fifty,
now it seems to be increasing further,
yesterday we told you that 10 global
companies are harassed for buying BPCL
and soon you can see more action on its disinvestment
and for Noida,
I am telling you about the buying, English has been
Salman